so here are two interactions i had with white people today some white folks was standing outside
the post office with a sign talking about some lady running for president and it said
make america good again so you know i hopped out and said when was america good
and then they had like pictures of presidents and of course this old white man said well
what about lincoln so because i'm black he jumped straight to the man on the brown coin
i said what about lincoln lincoln carried out the largest mass execution against native americans
no no that was andrew jackson i said do you think multiple presidents did not
genocide native americans and he said well stop being so skeptical
and i said you know it's just rich that a white man would sit up here and tell me about stop being
skeptical and he said well they fought the british empire what about that i said i'm going inside
while i was inside um i was talking to the the post guy the post man who's the homie so we talking and
then a white lady came up and asked about turning in her taxes and like could she just send them like
this and so as she was walking away i was like um you know they spend that money on wars and she said
yeah i know but if i don't pay they're gonna come after me and then i turned to the post man i said
i'm tired of white people today he said man listen we could shut shit down and throw folks for a loop
but that woman's mindset and that man's mindset speak so much of the american mindset of liberals
the issue is not republicans and maga the issue is liberals you all are the issue you all who believe
in democrats you all who don't think you're racist you all who will protect yourselves at all costs
dr king said this in 1967 that liberals desire to hold order and preserve order is what gets in the
way of shaking shit up you are what's keeping us from even being able to manage what's already
going to happen regardless which is the collapse of this empire support a real one